Privacy Policy
==============

**Introduction**

**‍**Emma Technologies LTD. ("we" or "us"), is a company registered in England and Wales whose registered office is at 49-51 Central Street, London, England, EC1V 8AB and whose registered number is 10578464. We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and to providing clear information about the use of your data. We are the data controller for the purposes of the personal data we collect via our website and for the performance of the services listed under the usages of your personal data, below (together, the “Services”). We are registered with the Information Commissioner's Office (the ICO) with registration number: ZA241546.

‍

**Use of our online Services**

_Collection of personal data_

_‍_When you use our Services we will have access to your personal data that you submit to us and personal data held by Account Servicing Payment Service Providers (i.e. any payment service provider, such as a bank or a credit card issuer that maintains an online payment account on your behalf) (“ASPSPs”) (“Personal Data”) for the duration of the transmission. Such Personal Data may include your date of birth, gender, account information, account balance, transactions, information on loans, insurance data and investments data. The manner in which we access, use, process and store your personal data for the provision of the Services is set out below.

_Contacts list_

Emma transmits the contacts lists on your phone so you can easily make payments to your contacts using the Emma app. You can, of course, choose not to sync your contacts list with Emma. This means that you won't be able to identify which of your mobile phone contacts are Emma customers.

‍_Images_

Emma stores the image that you decide to upload when attaching a receipt to a transaction, verifying your identity with us or adding a profile picture to your profile. You can, of course, choose not to upload any of this data.  

‍

**Personal Data**

**‍**_Use of your personal data_

In order to access and use the main functionality of our Services, we will direct you to use one of our trusted service providers or an ASPSP that implements Open Banking in order to transmit and access information (including personal data) relating to payment accounts (“Account Information”) that you hold with ASPSPs to us.

The information we collect and process will be used to run the Services.

‍

**Consent**

We’ll be able to access your Account Information (including any Personal data), if you give us explicit consent.

‍_How do I withdraw my consent?_

If after you provided your consent, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent by contacting us at our address or at the email address set out in the contact information above.

‍

**Deletion of Personal Data**

We will not keep your Personal Data for longer than necessary. We will delete your Personal Data as soon as it is no longer needed to provide the Services to you or upon termination of the Terms of Service. To request your data to be deleted, please contact live chat in the app, use the delete function in your profile settings page, or send us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://emma-app.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Your data will be deleted within 30 days from your request.

Just to let you know, as a regulated financial services provider, we must keep certain customer personal data even when you ask us to delete it. If you've closed your Emma account, we may not be able to delete your entire file because these regulatory responsibilities take priority. We'll generally keep your personal data for seven years after our business relationship with you ends, or such period as may be required by applicable local laws.

‍

**Disclosure**

We may share your Personal Data with selected third parties, including business partners, suppliers and subcontractors that assist us in the provision of our Service to you. The third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information as instructed by us to provide Services to you.

‍

‍**Keeping Your Personal Information Secure**

**‍**We take the security of your personal information very seriously and have appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures in place to help protect your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure as required by law in England.

Once we have received your User Information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access including: by encrypting any Personal Information which we transfer to our banking partner; and having in place an agreement with our banking partner which requires it to have in place appropriate measures to safeguard the security of the Personal Information we send to them.

‍

**Your Rights**

_Subject Access Requests_

You have the right to ask us to provide any personal data we have collected about You, to You. Should You wish to do so, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://emma-app.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to make a subject access request detailing:

* your name,
* your address,
* the period of data you’d like access to.

_Making a complaint to a supervisory authority_

Should you be dissatisfied with the service we provide, You have the right to file a formal complaint to the Information Commissioner's Office at [www.ico.org.uk](https://ico.org.uk/).

‍

**Changes To This Policy**

**‍**If we change this policy, we will post the revised policy here with an updated effective date. If we make significant changes to the policy, we may also notify you by other means such as sending an email or posting a notice on our home page.

‍

‍**Cookies Policy**

**‍**We collect data about how you interact with our website through the use of cookies. Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. You can find out more information about cookies at www.allaboutcookies.org. We use cookies to enhance the online experience of our visitors and to better understand how our Site is used. Cookies may tell us, for example, whether you have visited our site before or whether you are a new visitor. They can also help to ensure that adverts you see online are more relevant to you and your interests. When you browse the Site, we automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. When you use our website (the “Site”), our third parties may be placing and reading cookies (or web beacons) to collect information as a result of ad serving. For further information, [How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).
